{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875813167","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875813167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" f77b284c-e6bf-4edc-bae3-8dd365bf1575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875825233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875825233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" f77b284c-e6bf-4edc-bae3-8dd365bf1575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875833747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875833746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" f77b284c-e6bf-4edc-bae3-8dd365bf1575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875844955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875844955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" f77b284c-e6bf-4edc-bae3-8dd365bf1575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875846016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875846016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" f77b284c-e6bf-4edc-bae3-8dd365bf1575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875851176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875851176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" f77b284c-e6bf-4edc-bae3-8dd365bf1575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875867924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875867924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875868147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875868146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875869110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875869110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875870385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875870385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875875611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875875611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875880030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875880030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875880346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875880346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875881580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875881580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875885592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875885592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875886576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875886575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875886830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875886829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875887773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875887773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875890629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875890629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875891671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875891671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875892157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875892157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875896695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875896695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875896803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875896803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_120305"," gameId":" e229cbde-904d-4ce9-b954-965db3f7b069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}